Lincoln Filene Center Records UA018
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Publications, 1952 -- 1998; UA018.003; 2.65 Linear Feet; 58 Volumes; 12 Digital Object(s)
  - Educational Teleconferencing in Massachusetts: Project Evaluation for the MA Corporation for Educational Telecommunications' "Invisible Experiences: Looking Back and Ahead", 1987; UA018.003.067.00012 (Box 67)
  - Project Evaluation for the MA Corporation for Educational Telecommunications' Physics Forum, 1987; UA018.003.067.00013 (Box 67)
  - Joint Committee on Civic Education Research and Theory Working Committtee - Conference Transcript, 1965; UA018.003.067.00014 (Box 67)
  - Urban Renewal: Planners and People (Teacher's Guide), 1966; UA018.003.067.00015 (Box 67)
  - Technology: The Culture of Machine Living (Teacher's Guide), 1969; UA018.003.067.00016 (Box 67)
  - Prisons: Do They Need Reforming?, 1972; UA018.003.067.00017 (Box 67)
  - Prisons: Do They Need Reforming? (Teacher's Guide), 1972; UA018.003.067.00018 (Box 67)
  - The Governing Process: A Structure for Social Discipline, 1965; UA018.003.067.00019 (Box 67)
  - Reexamining the Roles and Relationships of Voluntary Organizations and Government, 1995; UA018.003.067.00020; O'Connell, Brian (Box 67)
  - Reflections on Training as a Capacity-Building Strategy, 1996; UA018.003.067.00021; Gooding, Cheryl (Box 67)
  - Community Service Learning in the Boston Public Schools, 1994-95 Program Book, 1994 -- 1995; UA018.003.067.00022 (Box 67)
  - Community Service Learning in the Boston Public Schools, 1992-94 Program Book, 1992 -- 1994; UA018.003.067.00023 (Box 67)
  - Community Service Learning in the Boston Public Schools, 1995 -- 1997; UA018.003.067.00024 (Box 67)
  - Sustainable Development in Practice: A Case Study in Analysis of Coastal Enterprises, Inc.'s Experience, 1997; UA018.003.067.00025 (Box 67)
  - New England Environmental Organization Directory, 1989; UA018.003.067.00026 (Box 67)
  - New England Environmental Organization Directory, 1993; UA018.003.067.00027 (Box 67)
  - Community Service Learning in the Boston Public Schools, 1994 -- 1998; UA018.003.067.00028 (Box 67)
  - Challenge to Leadership, 1987; UA018.003.067.00029 (Box 67)
  - New Frontiers in the Social Studies, 1965; UA018.003.067.00030; Gibson, John S. (Box 67)
  - Can We Create a "City of Light"?, 1961; UA018.003.067.00031; Turley, Joseph F. (Box 67)
    The Crisis in the Community.
  - Community Service Learning (Workshop at University Teaching Conference), 1996; UA018.003.067.00032 (Box 67)
  - Labor-Management Relations in the United States: Some Lessons and Perspectives for the 1970s, 1974; UA018.003.067.00033 (Box 67)
  - Studies on Intolerance in American Life, 1970; UA018.003.067.00034 (Box 67)
  - Volunteer Needs, Contributions, and Opportunities in Eastern Massachusetts, 1988; UA018.003.067.00035 (Box 67)
  - Education of Adolescents, 1985; UA018.003.067.00036 (Box 67)
  - Effective Citizenship: Upton Sinclair and The Jungle (Teacher's Manual), 1968; UA018.003.067.00037 (Box 67)
  - Technolgy: The Culture of Machine Living, 1972; UA018.003.067.00038 (Box 67)
  - The Youth Citizenshop Volunteer Program, 1990; UA018.003.067.00039 (Box 67)
  - Ideology and World Affairs (Teacher's Guide), 1963; UA018.003.067.00040 (Box 67)
  - The "X" Goes Here, 1956; UA018.003.067.00041 (Box 67)
  - Liberty and the Law, 1955; UA018.003.067.00042 (Box 67)
  - Work without Strife, 1952; UA018.003.067.00043 (Box 67)
  - Why Don't They Think!, 1952; UA018.003.067.00044 (Box 67)
  - Get Into the Game, 1955; UA018.003.067.00045 (Box 67)
  - Bread and Butter Plus, 1955; UA018.003.067.00046 (Box 67)
  - These Americans, 1952; UA018.003.067.00047 (Box 67)
  - A Students Guide to Environmental Programs in New England Colleges and Universities, 1990; UA018.003.067.00048 (Box 67)
  - The Citizen Survey Program, 1984; UA018.003.067.00049 (Box 67)
  - A Five Year Progress Report of the Lincoln Filene Center, 1980-84, 1985; UA018.003.067.00050 (Box 67)
  - Analysis of the Market for the Master of Science Graduate Program in Computer Science at Tufts University, 1983; UA018.003.067.00051 (Box 67)
  - An Evaluation: Project Era: Bellingham's Consideration of an Extended School Year, 1973; UA018.003.067.00052 (Box 67)
  - Youth Service in Massachusetts, 1990; UA018.003.067.00053 (Box 67)
  - Current Affairs and the Social Studies, 1968; UA018.003.067.00054 (Box 67)
  - How to Write a Proposal, 1983; UA018.003.067.00055 (Box 67)
  - Forum on Planning Alternatives for Franklin Park, 1975; UA018.003.067.00056 (Box 67)
  - The Stereotype, 1960; UA018.003.067.00057 (Box 67)
  - Into 1988: A Special Report, UA018.003.067.00058 (Box 67)
  - Kernels of Democracy, 1994; UA018.003.067.00059; Thomson, Ken; Berry, Jeffrey M.; Portney, Kent E. (Box 67)
  - Community Empowerment, 1994; UA018.003.067.00060; Thomson, Ken (Box 67)
  - The Theory and Practice of Citizen Participation: A Bibliography, 1975; UA018.003.067.00061 (Box 67)
  - Development of Curriculum in American Civilization for the General Student: Case Study Approach 1 of 2, 1969; UA018.003.067.00062 (Box 67)
  - Development of Curriculum in American Civilization for the General Student: Case Study Approach 2 of 2, 1969; UA018.003.067.00063 (Box 67)
  - Welfare: A Way of Life?, 1968; UA018.003.068.00001 (Box 68)
  - Environmental Protection and Foreign Aid: Institutional Reform, 1984; UA018.003.068.00002 (Box 68)
  - Financing Sustainable Development, 1985; UA018.003.068.00003 (Box 68)
  - Managing Environmental Risk in Newly Industrializing Countries, 1987; UA018.003.068.00004 (Box 68)
  - Reshaping Institutions to MEet Environmental Crises: Beyond Business as Usual, 1989; UA018.003.068.00005 (Box 68)
  - The Future of Boston Area Nonprofits, 1998; UA018.003.068.00006 (Box 68)
  - The Massachusetts Department of Education Proposals for Progress in the '70's, 1970; UA018.003.068.00007 (Box 68)
  - Citizen Action and Social Change: A Bibliography, 1984; UA018.003.068.00008; Elias, Robert; Woodbridge, Michael P. (Box 68)
  - Proceeding from the forum on The Pesticide Dilemma, 1984; UA018.003.068.00009 (Box 68)
  - Massachusetts and the World: An Activity and Resource Book, 1983; UA018.003.068.00010; Mulloy, Paul T. (Box 68)
  - Redefining Success in Community Development, 1994; UA018.003.068.00011 (Box 68)
  - Headaches, Tears, and Healing, 1995; UA018.003.068.00012 (Box 68)
  - Quest for Funds: Insider's Guide to Corporate and Foundation Funding, 1989; UA018.003.068.00013 (Box 68)
  - They Made a Nation, 1952; UA018.003.068.00014 (Box 68)
  - Annual Report, 1983 -- 1984; UA018.003.068.00015 (Box 68)
  - Environmental Action, 1984; UA018.003.068.00016 (Box 68)
  - Environmental Action, 1985; UA018.003.068.00017 (Box 68)
  - Massachusetts Department of Education: Operations, Functions, and Proposals, 1 of 2, 1970; UA018.003.068.00018 (Box 68)
  - Massachusetts Department of Education: Operations, Functions, and Proposals, 2 of 2, 1970; UA018.003.068.00019 (Box 68)
  - Public Affairs and the High School, 1962; UA018.003.068.00020 (Box 68)
  - Boyhood and Citizenship, 1964; UA018.003.068.00021 (Box 68)
  - Man and Politics, 1965; UA018.003.068.00022 (Box 68)
  - It Has Been Done!, 1952; UA018.003.068.00023 (Box 68)
  - Public Assistance since the Social Security Act: The Federal Impact in Massachusetts, 1969; UA018.003.068.00024 (Box 68)
  - Welfare and the Recipient, 1969; UA018.003.068.00025 (Box 68)
  - The Politics of Welfare, 1969; UA018.003.068.00026 (Box 68)
  - The Social Work Profession and Public Welfare, 1969; UA018.003.068.00027 (Box 68)
  - .... and Crown thy Good, 1952; UA018.003.068.00028 (Box 68)
  - ...and Crown thy Good (Teacher's Guide), 1952; UA018.003.068.00029 (Box 68)
  - Some Practical Observations and Suggestions on the Merit System, 1967; UA018.003.068.00030 (Box 68)
  - Labor Perspective on the Civil Service: The Role of Unionism, 1967; UA018.003.068.00031 (Box 68)
  - A Program of Achieving Excellence in the Civil Service, 1967; UA018.003.068.00032 (Box 68)
  - Legislative and Executive Responsibilities Toward the Character and Staffing of the Public Service, 1967; UA018.003.068.00033 (Box 68)
  - Students and the State: Campus Images of the Massachusetts Public Service, 1967; UA018.003.068.00034 (Box 68)
  - "The Public Welfare": Subtopics for Discussion Groups, 1967; UA018.003.068.00035 (Box 68)
  - Health Care Accessibility for Boston's Chinese Community 1 of 3, 1975; UA018.003.068.00036 (Box 68)
  - Health Care Accessibility for Boston's Chinese Community 2 of 3, 1975; UA018.003.068.00037 (Box 68)
  - Health Care Accessibility for Boston's Chinese Community 3 of 3, 1975; UA018.003.068.00038 (Box 68)
  - Capitalism: Way of Freedom, 1952; UA018.003.068.00039 (Box 68)
  - On Quality Education, 1970; UA018.003.068.00040 (Box 68)
  - Men to Remember, 1956; UA018.003.068.00041 (Box 68)
  - Citizenship, 1968; UA018.003.068.00042 (Box 68)
  - Forum on the Mystic and Aberjona River System, 1974; UA018.003.068.00043 (Box 68)
  - The Development of Instructional Materials Pertaning to Race and Culture in American Life, 1967; UA018.003.068.00044 (Box 68)
  - Educational Aspects of Delinquency: Its Implications for Vocational Rehabilitation, 1967; UA018.003.068.00045 (Box 68)
  - Citizenship Education: Academic and Pragmatic Perspectives, 1967; UA018.003.068.00046 (Box 68)
  - Learning Materials and Minorities: What Medium and What Message?, 1967; UA018.003.068.00047 (Box 68)
  - Youth and Adult Values Study, 1966; UA018.003.068.00048 (Box 68)
  - The Publisher as Teacher, 1966; UA018.003.068.00049 (Box 68)
  - The Political Significance of the European Economic Integration, 1970; UA018.003.068.00050 (Box 68)
  - Parents and Youth Facing Juvenile Maladjustments, 1966; UA018.003.068.00051 (Box 68)
  - The Young as Citizens, 1960; UA018.003.068.00052 (Box 68)
  - Toward Integration through Education: Dichotomies of Purposes and Progress, 1971; UA018.003.068.00053 (Box 68)
  - Education and Integration: Goals, Processes, and Innovations, 1971; UA018.003.068.00054 (Box 68)
  - Quality in Education: Challenge to Change, 1970; UA018.003.068.00055 (Box 68)
  - The Future of the Environmental Movement, 1980; UA018.003.068.00056 (Box 68)
  - Learning Interests and Needs of Environmental Leaders in New England, 1978; UA018.003.068.00057 (Box 68)
  - Freshwater Wetlands: Their Nature and Importance to Man, 1978; UA018.003.068.00058 (Box 68)
  - How to Use the Media Effectively, 1978; UA018.003.068.00059 (Box 68)
  - The Adolescent Citizen and the Junior High School, 1962; UA018.003.068.00060 (Box 68)
  - Economics and the High School Student, 1963; UA018.003.068.00061 (Box 68)
  - Civil Disobedience: A Higher Law?, 1969; UA018.003.068.00062 (Box 68)
  - Civil Disobedience: A Higher Law? (Teacher's Guide), 1969; UA018.003.068.00063 (Box 68)
  - Citizenship Denied: Diary of a Young Girl, 1969; UA018.003.068.00064 (Box 68)
  - Citizenship Denied: Diary of a Young Girl (Teacher's Guide), 1969; UA018.003.068.00065 (Box 68)
  - Citizenship Affirmed: The Story of Frederick Douglass, 1968; UA018.003.068.00066 (Box 68)
  - Citizenship Affirmed: The Story of Frederick Douglass (Teacher's Guide), 1968; UA018.003.068.00067 (Box 68)
  - Police: Liberty and Order in Conflict, 1973; UA018.003.068.00068 (Box 68)
  - The Future, 1972; UA018.003.068.00069 (Box 68)
  - Government Control: The Environment, 1971; UA018.003.068.00070 (Box 68)
  - The Candidate, 1972; UA018.003.068.00071 (Box 68)
  - Choosing a President, 1968: The American Political Process, 1969; UA018.003.068.00072 (Box 68)
  - Choosing a President, 1968: The American Political Process (Teacher's Guide), 1969; UA018.003.068.00073 (Box 68)
  - The Alliance for Progress: Trade and Aid in International Politics, 1968; UA018.003.068.00074 (Box 68)
  - The Courts Make Policy: The Story of Clarence Earl Gideon (Teacher's Guide), 1969; UA018.003.068.00075 (Box 68)
  - The Courts Make Policy: The Story of Clarence Earl Gideon, 1969; UA018.003.068.00076 (Box 68)
  - Conflict in the Middle East, 1969; UA018.003.068.00077 (Box 68)
  - Click and Tell: A Program for Elementary School Education, 1970; UA018.003.068.00078 (Box 68)
  - Effective Citizenship: Upton Sinclair and The Jungle (Teacher's Manual), 1968; UA018.003.069.00001 (Box 69)
  - The Dominican Republic: Engagement in Conflict, 1968; UA018.003.069.00002 (Box 69)
  - Gun Control: A Bill Becomes a Law, 1969; UA018.003.069.00003 (Box 69)
  - Gun Control: A Bill Becomes a Law (Teacher's Guide), 1969; UA018.003.069.00004 (Box 69)
  - Domestic Sources of Foreign Policy: The Marshall Plan, 1969; UA018.003.069.00005 (Box 69)
  - The Police: Fact and Fiction, 1968; UA018.003.069.00006 (Box 69)
  - The Police: Fact and Fiction (Teacher's Guide), 1968; UA018.003.069.00007 (Box 69)
  - Pictures as Bridges: A Program for Elementary School Education, 1970; UA018.003.069.00008 (Box 69)
  - The Question of Human Rights: The Olympic Boycott Threat, 1969; UA018.003.069.00009 (Box 69)
  - The Prevention of conflict: The Lebanese Crisis of 1958, 1969; UA018.003.069.00010 (Box 69)
  - The NATO Commitment, 1968; UA018.003.069.00011 (Box 69)
  - Nation Building in Ghana, 1968; UA018.003.069.00012 (Box 69)
  - The Black Power Revolt, 1972; UA018.003.069.00013 (Box 69)
  - The Civil Rights Movement (Teacher's Guide), 1972; UA018.003.069.00014 (Box 69)
  - Legal Education Materials for Elementary and Intermediate Grades, 1972; UA018.003.069.00015 (Box 69)
  - The Civil Rights Movement, 1971; UA018.003.069.00016 (Box 69)
  - Slavery: The Destructive Institution, 1970; UA018.003.069.00017 (Box 69)
  - Prejudice and Discrimination, 1970; UA018.003.069.00018 (Box 69)
  - The Hungarian Revolution, 1968; UA018.003.069.00019 (Box 69)
  - How Our Economic System Works (Teacher's Guide), 1969; UA018.003.069.00020 (Box 69)
  - Effective Citizenship: Upton Sinclair and The Jungle (Evaluative Instrument), 1968; UA018.003.069.00021 (Box 69)
  - Citizenship Affirmed: The Autobiography of Frederick Douglass (Evaluative Instrument), 1968; UA018.003.069.00022 (Box 69)
  - Effective Citizenship: Upton Sinclair and The Jungle, 1969; UA018.003.069.00023 (Box 69)
  - Youth and Community: The Massachusetts Youth Service Board and Juvenile Delinquency, 1960; UA018.003.069.00024 (Box 69)
  - The Young as Citizens, 1960; UA018.003.069.00025 (Box 69)
  - The State's Responsibility for its Youth, 1960; UA018.003.069.00026 (Box 69)
  - Studies on Idealism in American Life, 1969; UA018.003.069.00027 (Box 69)
  - Urban Renewal: Planners and People, 1968; UA018.003.069.00028 (Box 69)
  - To Buy a Car, 1969; UA018.003.069.00029 (Box 69)
  - To Buy a Car (Teacher's Guide), 1969; UA018.003.069.00030 (Box 69)
  - Technology: The Culture of Machine Living, 1972; UA018.003.069.00031 (Box 69)
  - Studies on Protest and Dissent in American life, 1969; UA018.003.069.00032 (Box 69)
  - Practical Political Action, 1962; UA018.003.070.001 (Box Volume 70)
  - State Government and Public Responsibility, 1962; UA018.003.071.001 (Box Volume 71)
    This is a soft bound book, but there is also a hard bound book of this volume with a different front cover.
  - State Government and Public Responsibility, Vol. IV, 1962; UA018.003.071.002 (Box Volume 2)
    This is the hard cover book. We have the soft-bound book as well.
  - State Government and Public Responsibility, 1964; UA018.003.072.001; Robbins, R. Prof. (Box Volume 72)
  - Environmental Leadership, 1984; UA018.003.073.001 (Box Volume 73)
  - The Development of Instructional Materials and Teaching Strategies on Race and Culture in American Life, volume 1, 1968; UA018.003.074.001 (Box Volume 74)
  - Justice: Fair Procedure for the Accused, 1963; UA018.003.075.001 (Box Volume 75)
  - The Development of Instructional Materials Pertaining to Race and Culture in America Cooperative Research Project No. H-199, 1966; UA018.003.076.001 (Box Volume 76)
  - Can "Anyone" Help the Homeless?, 1988; UA018.003.077.001 (Box Volume 77)
  - Goals for Students Means for Teachers, 1965; UA018.003.078.001 (Box Volume 78)
  - The Development of Instructional Materials and Teaching Strategies on Race and Culture in American Life, volume 2, 1968; UA018.003.079.001 (Box Volume 79)
  - A Program for Elementary School Education, 1969; UA018.003.080.001 (Box Volume 80)
  - Citizen Participation Perspectives Proceedings of the National Conference on Citizen Participation, 1978; UA018.003.081.001; Langton, Stuart (Box Volume 81)
  - Environmental handbook for Massachusetts Conservation Commissioners, 1978; UA018.003.082.001 (Box Volume 82)
  - National Puerto Rican Coalition Field Advocacy Program Assessment Report, 1990; UA018.003.083.001 (Box Volume 83)
  - Economics and the New England Environment, 1977; UA018.003.084.001 (Box Volume 84)
  - Report to UNESCO on the Effect of Intervention of In-school and Out-of-School Education Programs on the Social Adaptation of Youth in Metropolitan Boston Area, 1965; UA018.003.085.001 (Box Volume 85)
  - The Massachusetts Assembly on State Government Participants' Edition Background Papers, 1959; UA018.003.086.001 (Box Volume 86)
  - The Massachusetts Department of Education Proposals for Progress in the '70's, 1970; UA018.003.087.001 (Box Volume 87)
  - Negro Self-Concept: Implications for School and Citizenship, Juvenile Delinquency and Youth Development, 1964; UA018.003.088.001 (Box Volume 88)
  - Secondary Education for Disadvantaged Urban Youth, 1964; UA018.003.089.001 (Box Volume 89)
  - The Greening of Boston, An Action Agenda, 1987; UA018.003.090.001 (Box Volume 90)
  - The Development of Appropriate Instructional Units and Related Materials on Racial and Cultural Diversity in America, 1967; UA018.003.091.001 (Box Volume 91)
  - Participation Works, 1994; UA018.003.092.001; Thomson, Ken; Bissetta, Joanne; Webb, Thomas (Box Volume 92)
  - Massachusetts Crime Commission, Fifth Report, 1965; UA018.003.093.001 (Box Volume 93)
  - American Public Diplomacy: The Perspective of Fifty Years, 1967; UA018.003.094.001; Delaney, Robert F.; Gibson, John S. (Box Volume 94)
    Edward R. Murrow Center; Lincoln Filene Center
  - State Government and Public Responsibility, 1961; UA018.003.095.001 (Box Volume 95)
  - Ideology and World Affairs, 1967; UA018.003.096.001 (Box Volume 96)
  - High Schools for a Free Society, 1960; UA018.003.097.001 (Box Volume 97)
  - State Government and Public Responsibility, 1959; UA018.003.098.001; Robbins, R. Prof. (Box Volume 98)
  - Practical Political Action: a guide for citizens, 1970; UA018.003.099.001; Gibson, John S. (Box Volume 99)
  - State Government and Public Responsibility, 1963; UA018.003.100.001 (Box Volume 100)
  - Law and Disorder, 1968; UA018.003.101.001 (Box Volume 101)
  - Capitalism: Way of Freedom (revised edition), 1957; UA018.003.102.001 (Box Volume 102)
  - What about War?, 1957; UA018.003.103.001 (Box Volume 103)
  - Massachusetts Politics, 1960; UA018.003.104.001; Latham, Earl; Goodwin, George Jr. (Box Volume 104)
  - Civil Liberties: Case Studies and the Law, 1965; UA018.003.105.001 (Box Volume 105)
  - The Intergroup Relations Curriculum A Program for Elementary School Education, vol. 2, 1969; UA018.003.106.001; Gibson, John S. (Box Volume 106)
  - Public Welfare in Massachusetts, 1967; UA018.003.107.001 (Box Volume 107)
  - The Public Servant: non-elective government service in Massachusetts, 1966; UA018.003.108.001; Seasholes, Brad (Box Volume 108)
  - State Government and Public Responsibility, 1963; UA018.003.109.001 (Box Volume 109)
  - Public Education in Massachusetts: Problems and Challenges, 1965; UA018.003.110.001; Seasholes, Brad (Box Volume 110)
  - National Civic Review: Citizen Participation, 1987; UA018.003.111.001 (Box Volume 111)
    Volume 76, Number 4, July-August 1987; Part 2 of 3; See also 39090014014571b and 39090014014589b for parts 1 and 3
    Volume, issue
    76, 4
  - The Adolescent Citizen, 1960; UA018.003.112.001 (Box Volume 112)
  - The Isms and You, 1957; UA018.003.113.001 (Box Volume 113)
  - The Martha's Vimeyard Cable Connection, 1982; UA018.003.114.001 (Box Volume 114)
  - Race and Culture in American Life, 1967; UA018.003.115.001 (Box Volume 115)
  - State Government and Public Responsibility, 1960; UA018.003.116.001 (Box Volume 116)
  - Negro Self Concept Conference Report, 1965; UA018.003.117.001 (Box Volume 117)
  - Negro Self-Concept: Implications for School and Citizenship, 1965; UA018.003.118.001; Gibson, John S. (Box Volume 118)
  - Intergroup Relations Curriculum, v. 1, 1969; UA018.003.119.001 (Box Volume 119)
  - Ideology and World Affairs, 1964; UA018.003.120.001; Gibson, John S. (Box Volume 120)
  - Ideology and World Affairs, revised edition, 1967; UA018.003.121.001; Gibson, John S. (Box Volume 121)
  - State Government and Public Responsibility, Vol. III, 1961; UA018.003.122.001 (Box Volume 122)
  - National Civic Review: Citizen Participation, 1987; UA018.003.123.00001 (Box Volume 123)
    Volume 76, Number 3, May-June 1987; Part 1 of 3; See also 39090011489214b and 39090014014589b for parts 2 and 3
    76, 3
  - National Civic Review: Citizen Participation, 1987; UA018.003.124.00001 (Box Volume 124)
    Volume 76, Number 5, September-October 1987; Part 3 of 3; See also 39090011489214b and 39090014014571b for parts 1 and 2
    6, 5
  - Law and Disorder, 1968; UA018.003.125.00001 (Box Volume 125)
    Volume X of a series on State Government and Public Responsibility, edited from the papers and proceedings of the Tufts Assembly on Massachusetts Government; See also 39090011488794
  - Massachusetts Politics: Some Limitations and Prospects, 1965; UA018.003.126.00001 (Box 126)
  - Studies on Intolerance in American Life (Teacher's Guide), 1969; UA018.003.126.00002 (Box 126)
  - Studies on Idealism in American Life (Teacher's Guide), 1969; UA018.003.126.00003 (Box 126)
  - Studies on Protest and Dissent in American life (Teacher's Guide), 1969; UA018.003.126.00004 (Box 126)
  - How our economic system works, 1968; UA018.003.126.00005 (Box 126)
  - Tufts Assembly on Massachusetts Government - Law and Disorder, 1968; UA018.003.126.00006 (Box 126)
- Additional accessions, UA018.000839
  - Lincoln Filene Center, newsletters, pamphlets and brochures., 1962 -- 1997; UA018-001 (Box UA018-001)
    20 years from date of creation.
  - Lincoln Filene Center various files, UA018-002 (Box UA018-002)
  - Lincoln Filene Center various files, UA018-003 (Box UA018-003)
  - Extras from CONF and NEEC'94 [New England Environmental Conference], 1994; UA018-004 (Box UA018-004)
  - 4th Cabinet/5th Drawer, Misc. [CEM subject/general files: Childhood Lead Poisoning NEEC, Support Center of Mass], UA018-005 (Box UA018-005)
  - 4th Filing Cabinet, 3rd Drawer "Exhibits" [New England Environmental Conference 1996], UA018-006 (Box UA018-006)
  - 4th Filing Cabinet, 3rd Drawer "NEEC '94 Media Info, 1994 -- 1996; UA018-007 (Box UA018-007)
  - Cab. 4, top drawer CEP Filing 95; Goldberg Files Box 2 84-93; Public Service Fellows 93-94 Box 2, 1984 -- 1996; UA018-008 (Box UA018-008)
  - PSI Box 1 [Public Service Initiative], UA018-009 (Box UA018-009)
  - PSI Box 2 [Public Service Initiative], UA018-010 (Box UA018-010)
  - Public Service Fellows 93-94 Box 1, 1993 -- 1994; UA018-011 (Box UA018-011)
  - 12-23-02 LFC-UCCPS Old Program/Grants, UA018-012 (Box UA018-012)
  - LFC Info 1965, UA018-013 (Box UA018-013)
  - New England Environmental Network News; NonProfit Quarterly 94, 1978 -- 1994; UA018-014 (Box UA018-014)
  - Rob Hollister UEP 1989-91/Lincoln-Filene 91-97, 1984 -- 1997; UA018-015 (Box UA018-015)
  - Fundraising Classes Archive 2002 Rob Hollister; CRPI Director Search, UA018-016 (Box UA018-016)
  - Schramm Files, UA018-017 (Box UA018-017)
  - Goldberg Files, UA018-018 (Box UA018-018)
  - Archive, UA018-019 (Box UA018-019)
  - Acting Director, 1997; UA018-020 (Box UA018-020)